Hey, everybody.
Welcome to Chants of Sennaar.
I hope I'm pronouncing that right.
I thought it would be nice to intersperse a little bit of a shorter game in between the bigger ones I'm playing right now.
So, yeah.
Let's play this one.
Now, the only thing I know about this game is that it's apparently language-based.
And there's puzzles.
That's all I know.
Let's do it.
Yeah, just use that one.
That's fine.
New game.
I'm excited.
Rundisc.
Chants of Sennaar.
Okay.
Click on the background to move.
You can also choose to play with a controller.
Oh, that's very old-school-like.
I like that.
Wait, did I just emerge from that tombstone or something?
Also, look at me.
I have no face.
I'm wearing some kind of robe.
I look kind of silly.
Can I click on this or do something with it?
Right-click?
No.
All right.
Interesting art style.
I don't even know what to call this.
Simple, kind of monochrome, but still with a bit of color.
Type of wireframe?
Hatched?
Oh, I'm really liking this click-to-move thing.
That's been a while since I've done something like that in a game.
Can I do anything?
Oh, I can walk up there.
What's over here?
I'm loving this atmosphere in the back.
The sounds.
Are these illusory walls?
Why do they look like doors?
Oh, I'm running if I click.
That's nice.
Look at that.
A bit of a sprint there.
Very interesting art style.
I'm liking this look here.
Notice how the camera angle changes to very specific angles, too.
Okay, take me in there.
Someone made a hole in the wall.
Okay.
Got a bit of a river here.
Or a canal, I should say.
Chants of Sennaar.
I wonder if that's the name of the city I'm in right now.
Oh, whoa, whoa.
Oh, this is where I came from, I see.
Am I going to be chanting something?
Can't cross that.
It's too deep, apparently.
Don't want to get my ropes wet.
Click on an item to interact with it.
Ah, right.
Okay.
I'm liking the UI sounds.
It's so satisfying.
This journal will record all the glyphs you discover.
Okay.
To open it, click on the journal button.
You can also open it by clicking directly on a text.
Oh, I see.
I can also operate the handle.
When you think you have guessed the meaning of a glyph, you can click on it to note your hypothesis.
To exit the journal, click on the close button.
That one, I guess.
What's this?
Okay.
Oh, really?
Hello.
Oh, that's neat.
You can...
Okay, okay.
We got to figure out what these mean.
Oh, wait a minute.
This is a handle, right?
Opens the door?
Open and close, surely.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Ah, okay.
This has to mean open.
This has to mean close.
I'm just guessing that.
I don't know.
Um...
Oh, but wait a minute.
This consists of two glyphs.
This guy and that guy.
Oh, maybe open door.
Oh, wait a minute.
Does it say...
Close door?
Open door?
This has to mean door.
Door.
This one has to mean open.
Or gate.
It could also be gate, I guess.
Close.
Let's do a door slash gate.
I like that there's a question mark on it.
Does that mean I didn't guess it correctly?
Maybe when I get it correctly it will...
Oh, that's neat.
It combines them two.
That is so nice.
Yo, I'm liking this so far.
Holy shit, what's this?
Oh, it's the menu.
Right.
Okay, okay.
Very nice.
Ooh, I'm liking this so far.
I'm really liking this.
Get up here.
And I can open this at any time.
Neat.
Okay, so where am I now?
Why is nobody here?
And why did I emerge from that grave?
If needed, use the middle button to reveal all the interactive items in the surroundings.
A pulsating white dot indicates items where something is still to be seen or done.
Oh, nice.
That's actually kind of helpful.
Alrighty.
Ah, open, open, close, open, close, open.
So what constitutes open, though?
Open means let water through or open?
Oh, probably, yeah.
Open.
What was it?
Open, open, close.
Open, close, open.
Okay.
Open, open, close.
Open, close, open.
So this one needs to be open.
And that one needs to be open.
Yo, this is sick!
Oh, I'm liking this.
That is so nice.
So when we go over here, look at this.
It's presumably gonna tell me...
Yeah, look, it even says open, open, close, open, close, open because I already put names to the glyphs.
Okay, so every glyph here is one word.
Gotcha.
Confirmed.
So water's gone now.
Does that mean when I go back, the water's gonna be gone too?
Take me back.
No, the water's still down here.
Okay.
Run to over here.
There's also water up there.
Oh, that's what's powering these, I guess, these valves.
What's down here on the left?
Can I go in there somehow?
No.
Oh, I can also hold down the button.
Let's not forget.
Whoa!
Drag each glyph into the slot that you think matches it.
If all the glyphs on a double page are correct, they will be definitively validated.
Yo!
Okay!
Oh, lock, unlock?
Gate.
Boom.
Oh no, wait, I got it wrong.
This is unlock.
This is gate.
This is close.
Let's see what they actually are.
Open, door, close.
Yo, I fucking nailed it!
That's awesome!
The more glyphs you translate, the better you will understand your interlocutors.
If you haven't figured out the meaning of a glyph yet, or don't have enough slots in your journal, keep looking around.
What a great concept for a game.
Holy shit.
Uh, can I click on anything else?
No, okay.
Oh, that is neat, dude.
So when I click here now...
Yeah, that's nice.
Dude, I am freaking loving this!
Okay.
I mean, I know the puzzles are simple so far, but they're satisfying.
I'm having a blast with this already, this is crazy.
Head down this way.
Yo!
Okay, so water is a huge part of this game, it seems.
Aqueducts and...
the leading of water through a city.
Like a sewage system, almost, down there.
Oh, that's nice!
Look at how that looks!
Wonderful!
Okay, go up here.
Hello, he says?
How are you?
I'm guessing.
That has to mean hello.
It even looks like a little smiley, right?
Hello?
Uh, I'm just gonna guess how are you, but...
Okay, two lines, swingy and an L.
Two lines, swingy and an L.
How...
are...
you?
Oh, wait, maybe that's a question mark symbol, too, somehow.
Or maybe he says my name is?
No, I am...
Jack.
Wait, this means...
Uh...
You open door.
No, wait, how open door?
Oh, please open door!
Maybe it means please.
Maybe he says please help me.
That's probably what that means.
This means please.
He says please help me, please open door.
Help...
me.
Please open door.
I got you.
There we go.
He's some kind of head priest.
Or whatever.
He has some kind of thing on his head.
A half moon.
What if I close this again now?
What then?
Is that... Oh, that means I can go through now.
Right.
Ah, but I have to time this.
Check this out.
We operate this guy...
and quickly go.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Oh, I can't move while it's doing it.
Okay, never mind.
Never mind.
Oh, I can still pass.
I thought this was below water before.
Speak to me.
Yeah, now you open door.
Exactly!
Or I, maybe it means I open door.
But nobody would say please help I, right?
Yeah, me open door.
Go, go for it.
Go for it, buddy.
Hahaha!
Oh, I also get it now.
I was a little confused why he would call it open door when it's racing and lowering water levels.
But this is actually some kind of door, I guess.
He says thank you.
Or maybe he says please come.
Please come.
That's my guess on that.
I, I will come to you.
Or maybe please go.
Or please move.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, what's this?
He's waving saying hello.
Hello?
You, me.
Me?
Where's you?
Oh, wait a minute, maybe I got it wrong.
What did he say before?
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Let's see here.
Also, I like these drawings, they're very nice.
Oh, I can replay them too, that's nice.
So he says hello.
Uh, instead of him saying please help me, maybe he says, you help me.
Yeah, actually, maybe that would make more sense.
So this would be you.
You,
help me.
So that means over here, how can I cancel this?
And then he says you open door.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, that's nice.
I like that.
It has to be you.
Yes, I think I got it.
Oh, greetings.
Okay, yeah, well, that works.
Me, you.
That is awesome.
Look at these drawings here, by the way.
They have these slits to look through.
Very burka-esque.
And then we have this half moon on top, maybe signifying a higher standing or something in the circle of mages or whatever it is we're all part of.
Not quite sure what's going on here, I'm excited to figure it out.
These two, though, not entirely sure yet.
What did he say over here?
I'll open the door.
Wait, where's the aisle come from?
Oh, I guess it's me.
So you just have to use a bit of context awareness here.
To what makes sense with the rest of the sentence.
So he's technically saying me open the door, but it gets changed to aisle.
Got it.
That's neat.
You go, buddy.
I'm going to call him.
I don't know, Richard.
Good job, Richard.
I'll follow you.
And then he says, you come.
Maybe he says that or you go.
I would say probably go, but let's do both.
Come go.
Go up here.
Oh, this is great.
All right.
You open the door.
I will open the door.
Thank you, Richard.
And can I just say what a beautiful robe you have on.
It's wonderful.
Now he says, I'll go.
It has to mean go.
Come doesn't make sense here.
Go for it, buddy.
Me go.
Go for it.
Oh, right.
I have to click.
You close the door.
I mean, I was ready to take notes on my own here, but seems like the game has a system for it.
That's so good.
Now he says you go.
Exactly.
I go.
I go so hard right now.
What now, Richard?
He even has a small cape.
You help me.
I will help you.
There you go.
Oh, wait, that doesn't help you, does it?
Maybe it does, actually.
I go to the other side and I click on this guy.
And then I go over here so I can get to this thing, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just love the way I look.
Oh, wait.
Oh, I didn't pay attention here to the mechanics of the water.
So I have to cross here, which means this water needs to be let out to over here.
So we got to open this guy now.
I think.
Yes, it drains out this way.
Okay, now we go.
I can just click over here, I guess, and he will automatically run over there.
I love the way he runs.
Look at that.
I'm here, Richard.
Check this out.
Ah, but wait, I need to open this guy over here, too.
Otherwise, the water is not going to drain.
I get it.
Hold on, Richard.
I'll be there in a second.
Open this bad boy.
That should drain out completely.
Yes.
And now we click on this guy.
Oh, wait, he has something to say.
Or not.
I'm coming.
I'm coming, Richard.
Don't despair.
Also, nice to meet you.
My name is Johnny.
Goodbye.
Is that what that means?
Wait.
How do I know that?
How do I know what that means?
Oh, so greetings is also context based on, hey.
Saying hello and saying goodbye.
It's just waving, right?
Gotcha.
Okay, goodbye.
Oh, sorry.
I want to wave back at him.
Richard.
I wonder if this guy also arose from a stony grave.
Just like me.
That's going to replay this part.
Okay.
And off he went.
Interesting stuff.
Okay.
I still have a couple that I'm not quite sure of.
I'm pretty sure of Go.
Help?
Not entirely sure.
I think it's correct.
Let's go.
Dude, this is great.
Oh, we got drawings.
What's this?
Oh, wait, where did those come from?
Oh, down here.
Okay, so the sun was shining.
It dried out the land.
All the plants whittled away.
And that's why this city needs all this water.
Is this an aqueduct down here?
This could mean sun.
Shines?
Well, it would be guessing at this point, I guess.
I also don't want to put in something that is entirely incorrect.
You know, because it may mess up my mind later.
Because I get locked into thinking that it may be the answer.
The fact there's two L's.
Sun.
Plants.
And water.
Oh, but wait a minute.
This is one word, isn't it?
Sun?
One of them has to be sun.
This has to be a sun.
Ah, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on a minute.
Sun, sun.
This is just one L.
Notice how this L is also here in you.
Man, I wonder if this is a real actual language you could decipher.
Me, M-E?
Greetings?
Okay, never mind.
I was about to say maybe the amount of lines corresponds to letters.
Then again.
No, look at all these letters and greetings.
There's no way.
This one could make sense.
M and E.
U, three lines, right?
But this one doesn't really work.
I'm going to say maybe light.
It could be light.
Let's do sun slash light.
Then again.
Yeah, I don't know.
You know what?
I'm going to do a little star if I'm very unsure.
This guy could be...
Duh, I don't know.
I don't know.
What is the point of this up here?
Oh, it's cycling through the different...
Is it sentences?
Is this a whole sentence?
There's three letters in this one.
Or three words, I guess.
Wait a minute, though.
Can I go through earlier ones like this?
I cannot.
Okay.
Obviously, the water is here to sort of remedy the whole arid situation, right?
There's a drought, for sure.
That's why we're wearing these robes, maybe, to protect us against the sun.
Ah, but wait, there's more!
Holy shit, here we go!
We're praising the sun!
Yes!
Let me see.
This has to mean sun.
That's a sun symbol.
100%ofrendo.
That's sun.
Let's get rid of this.
Unsure about that.
Um, what else do we have?
Sun?
Sun is very nice.
Probably not.
But, uh...
I mean, we're definitely praising it, right?
Praise the sun.
Okay, so we have some L's over here again.
And this is four words.
One, two, three, four.
So, this L is one word.
Which I guess makes sense, because we have established that each of these different glyphs is one word, right?
Let's see what's over here.
Oh my god, it's the headmaster!
It's the guy we talked to!
It's Richard!
Richard is the master sun dude!
And there's different variations.
Okay.
That one gave us another one.
Oh man, okay, it's getting complicated.
I don't know what to call this.
Maybe a...
A senate, or a circle of sun bros.
Chants of Sennaar.
Man, I like this music.
That's very nice.
This L keeps popping up, though.
Let's see if there's more over here.
Not quite.
I want to take another look at these, though.
Notice how some of it is blocked off here, too.
Or not blocked off.
Some of it has fallen off, destroyed.
I think this is telling a story.
Maybe in ancient times, the sun was very hot.
And all the plants withered.
Then over here...
Maybe they were pleading to the sun, please don't kill us!
Please reduce your strength.
And then over here...
The sun obeyed, and we all became one with the sun.
I'm not sure.
Let's just keep going for a bit.
I want to see what else there is to see.
Oh, the dude is sitting right there!
It's this dude over here!
Let's call him...
Stanley.
Sup, Stanley?
Greetings.
Good to see you.
Oh, he says hello in this case.
Okay.
Oh, right.
I want to say hello, too.
You're not going to say anything else to me?
Okay.
Fine.
Ah, but we got more.
Okay.
So we have all the sun bros over here.
We got Richard.
We got Stanley.
They were all... There was five of them.
That's kind of important.
The wind is blowing.
This is most likely the city we're in right now.
Maybe this is Cenar.
And these guys are chanting.
Oh, is that what they're doing?
Maybe they're chanting towards the sun.
The sun, of course, is shining.
We walked to the sun.
No.
I don't know.
This is difficult.
Let's see what else we got here.
Okay.
I need to see all of these.
What's happening over here?
It's night now.
Oh.
They're saying, no, you cannot enter.
Maybe it's like a temple to the sun over here.
Close door.
Do not close door.
The door is closed.
The moon is out.
And stars.
Moon, stars close the door.
Sun opens the door.
Let's see what's on this one over here.
Oh, I just took some notes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, man.
We know what that is.
That sun.
It has to be.
I mean, maybe it's not the sun.
Maybe it is actually some kind of...
device made by humans put on top of this temple...
that releases all this sun.
Okay, so wait a minute.
Hold up.
I do not think it is actually the sun.
I mean, come on.
It's the sun symbol.
But I was thinking for a moment that maybe...
this civilization...
all their crops dried out because of, you know, this hot weather.
Or these sun rays coming in.
And then they tried to seek out the sun...
to stop this from happening.
But then it turned out that another civilization...
had built this giant crystal or whatever...
that emanated the sun-like rays...
and they pleaded for them to stop doing it.
And they were like, we can't do it.
Sorry.
The gate is closed.
Or...
perhaps they simply sought refuge.
Because everything died.
All the crops were gone.
And they were looking to hide out in the temple.
Or in Cenar.
But the fact that...
Stanley over here...
is here right now is kind of interesting.
Right?
Does that mean we finally got in?
You know, one day I got in.
Something like that.
I can't guess this right now.
I feel like this is too difficult.
Let's have a look at this again.
So this dude has a sword.
It could mean guard.
Actually.
This guy could be a guardian.
Yeah.
Now, of course, I'm not sure which symbol it is...
that I'm supposed to use there.
Let's see.
Guardians closed the door.
But why would you say guardians, guardians closed door?
Unless...
Maybe if you repeat the word twice, it simply means...
two guardians closed the door.
Yeah.
So it's an L with the little triangles.
Let's see here.
L with little triangles.
I'm gonna say this means guard.
Or guardian.
Or soldier.
Could also be a soldier, I guess.
Now, this is, of course, Richard.
He's holding up his hands.
Now we have this dude over here.
Is that me?
It does not look like me.
I don't have this sort of slit down my robe.
Like this, right?
Okay.
Let's see here.
Yeah.
I don't want to guess either, right?
I want to try and understand this first.
Let's see if we can recognize some of this now.
So...
This could mean approach.
Since there's two of these in a row, it could mean plural.
Just like guards, or two guards, right?
In this case, it could be...
I don't know what to call these people.
Maybe monks.
Let's call them monks for now.
Maybe they found the sun.
The monks found sun.
But then there's also something over here.
So there's something missing from the sentence, right?
On top of temple, perhaps.
Let's say this L with the thingies here are called monks.
Just monk.
Let's put a star on it because I'm not really sure.
Same with the guardian.
This one is very unsure as well.
Do not trust my own writing is what I'm telling myself here.
Ah, this music is wonderful.
Hey, bro.
Stanley, talk to me again.
What a polite little bow.
Must be so annoying running around with that big thing on your head.
Let's see here.
They are representing the sun.
Monk monk.
I want
to see the first one again.
This is a real mystery.
Sun.
So these are very unique to this image in particular.
I'm assuming that what is depicted in this sort of stone engraving here...
is what's being described down here.
This could mean sun rays...
or heat.
This could mean crops.
Or at least one of them could mean crops.
Actually, the fact that these guys are dying and withering...
maybe this means death.
It even looks like a person, an L, you know, either a guardian or a monk is lying down, aka dead.
I'm going to say that's death.
Just dead.
Also, very unsure.
It killed the crops, right?
The sun killed the crops.
Perhaps this means plants.
Yeah, because look, there's two of them.
It means plural.
Then again, if there's two of these over here...
Also, I'm assuming it means plural at this point.
I'm not sure.
That's the only thing that makes sense.
Let's say plants...
crops...
Yeah, very unsure about that one.
What could these L's mean?
We have these L's everywhere, right?
There's L's here and there's L's here.
You know what?
It could just mean people.
L could be people in general.
Then we have the L's with the triangles meaning specific kinds of people, meaning guardians.
Let's say people or person.
And then we have multiple, you have people, right?
Right.
The sun...
did something to the people.
What did it do?
What did the sun do?
The sun...
healed or gave life.
It bathed them in warmth.
I'm not sure about that one.
What did the sun do?
Nourished them.
Bathed them in sunlight.
Revitalized.
Ah, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
The sun shone its rays on the people.
And in turn, they became sun gods.
The sun made them into sun bros.
Look, the people, person persons became monks.
Let's change that monk to sun bro.
I like that.
Where is it?
Monks.
Sun bro.
That's what all these people are.
That's what Richard is.
That's what Stanley is.
Yep.
So they became infused with the power of the sun.
And then they sought out this place over here.
Or perhaps they built a temple to the sun.
Then again, it does look like they were approaching it, right?
And...
Sun bros.
Built a sun temple.
Let's say this is temple.
Or city.
Or Cenar.
Okay.
Let's keep going.
And then over here...
Guardians, guardians closed the door.
And we sank into despair because of that.
Interesting.
Alright.
Hey birdies.
Hey.
Okay, I can go up here.
Let's just keep going.
I want to see what's up here too.
Oh.
Another sun bro.
Or... sun sister?
You go door.
Guardian, guardians closed door.
Ooh, hold up a second.
You must go door.
The guardians have closed the door, look!
Yes!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
These mean guardians, 100%.
This could mean must.
You must...
close door.
Let's say must.
You must close door.
This, I think, is just a person.
This is a monk, aka sun bro.
Boom.
Yes!
Fuck yeah!
So what does it actually mean?
Man slash human.
Devotee, okay, yeah.
Close enough with the monk.
Warrior, alright.
God!
Wow, okay.
I guess we praised the sun so hard that to us it was God.
My oh my.
Oh, that's nice.
The warriors locked the door.
You must...
go door.
I must go over here and talk to them.
Thanks, man.
I will do it.
Excuse me, why have you closed this door?
Oh, calm down now, I have no weapon, sir.
What's this?
Oh, there's a whole new page.
Hold on, is this a different language?
This looks different.
Look at that.
These are all straight lines.
Here we have rounded lines, too.
I think they're speaking a different language here.
You cannot enter.
The door is closed.
The...
door...
is...
my guess.
Oh my God.
All right, all right.
And here we have them.
So, the gal down here said...
go door.
Guardian's closed door.
Right.
So what are you saying over here?
Okay, you're saying the same thing.
Hail.
Okay, calm down, calm down.
What are you saying?
Okay, he's saying something about God.
The temple, the city of the gods...
I need to go to the city.
The warriors...
Probably must is wrong here.
killed the devotees.
They locked the door.
Yeah.
If this means...
must...
and they're saying...
What are they saying over here again?
Ah, but hold on.
They're speaking a different language, right?
At least, I'm assuming here, I could be wrong.
What are you saying?
Oh, here we go.
The temple of the sun, or of the god.
God...
Oh, we've seen this symbol before.
I'm a devotee.
Yes?
I am also a devotee, I think.
Actually, I'm not, because I don't have that thing on my head.
Maybe I'm just a disciple.
God fears me.
Probably not.
Maybe God fuels me.
The city of God...
I need to go to it.
So we've seen this one before as well.
What are you saying?
Okay, the city of God.
You want to go there.
Yeah, this one definitely says, you need to help us.
Because me, me means us.
This one is confirmed being help.
Yeah.
So what could that one mean?
Me, me...
This could be must...
or need.
Could be must or need.
We've got to cross-check this with the...
with the stuff on the wall downstairs after.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, you want to go there.
So now that we know this, let's also talk to this guy again, by the way.
Okay.
Devotee.
Oh, I didn't mean to click on that, actually.
Look at these nice little images.
God, I love the simplicity of the UI and the cleanliness of the style.
You know what I mean?
It's very minimalistic, but clean.
It's awesome.
Even the sounds sound clean, if that even makes sense.
Okay.
Um...
The sun maybe calls me.
The God is calling me.
That could be a thing he's saying, right?
Requests me.
Need.
Could also be need.
I guess.
God calls me.
The city of God.
I got to go to the city.
Yeah, look, they're all standing here.
They want to get in, right?
But these guys are saying no.
You cannot.
The Warriors are saying no.
Okay, that was also a dude down here that I want to talk to.
You there.
You're sitting there reading something.
Whoa.
Oh, he's straight up telling me.
Oh.
Sorry.
What?
Excuse me?
Are we playing a game?
Wait, I'm so confused.
He got a ball?
I didn't.
Click on that one again.
City of God.
It's just God, actually.
God, Warrior.
Huh?
I'm not sure what's happening.
Let's try this one.
Okay, Warrior.
Human.
Oh, I need to pick two of the same things.
God, Human.
God.
And Devotee.
Huh?
I have no idea what I just did.
Let's try that again.
Okay, so we have...
Human Devo...
Dammit.
I... don't understand this.
Human.
And he's doing the other one.
Huh?
Okay.
Maybe he has to choose the...
opposite?
I don't get it.
Huh?
Okay, that makes no sense to me right now.
At all, like, I understand zero of what just occurred.
How did I gain points?
How did he gain points?
No idea.
Nice umbrella you got there, by the way.
Um, I can go up that way.
Oh, now that I know a couple more things...
You must go to door, the Warriors lock the door.
Right.
Uh, what could also be a replacement for must?
Could be need.
Yeah, so I have two of them that...
kind of seem like the same, but...
you know.
You must need go door.
Okay, could also mean please.
Okay, now that we know all that, let's take another look here.
I want to find this one particular... that one.
Devotee...
needs God.
That would make sense.
Right?
The devotees need God.
They need the sun.
Could also mean traveled.
You... if that means traveled, then the person up here would say something like, you traveled to the door, like go to the door.
But then again, we also have a word for go.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
I want to move on.
Let's go this way.
What do we have here?
Nice plants.
Can I sniff them?
We got a symbol up there.
This means something with house, or city, or...
temple, because...
I think that the temple symbol, this one...
there's two of them here, inside a box.
Right?
There's definitely some kind of connection.
I can pull this.
Is someone going to appear in the slit?
Yeah.
Hello.
All right.
Hey.
All right, man.
Hey, look a cat.
Aww.
Best game ever.
Do it again.
Oh, my God.
You're the best cat ever.
I want to hug that cat.
Man, what does that mean?
Oh, look at this, by the way.
If we go over here...
Oh, we still don't have any pages for this.
Okay, gotcha.
All right, I'll be back later, I guess.
Ooh.
Hey, little buddy.
You must need me.
No, I don't need you.
Go away.
What could that mean?
Follow me.
It means follow.
Wants me to follow, for sure.
Right?
Okay.
I follow you.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
That was a nice view, though.
Where did you go?
Hey, buddy.
You should have waited for me, kid.
Oh, wait, I can't go that way.
Did you go in here?
You didn't go in there, did you?
Open up!
You don't want me, huh?
All right, fine.
Let's head out this way.
There you are!
Look at you!
You found me!
Found.
Find.
I did!
Now it's my turn.
Count to ten.
You must need follow me.
Oh!
Okay, wait a minute, then.
You find me?
Could mean find.
Which suggests that the devotees found the sun.
They found God.
But then they were denied access to God.
It's fine.
100%.
Okay.
I'll find you.
So you went this way, huh?
Where are you hiding, huh?
You little rascal, you?
Hey, have you seen a little...
Have you seen a little kid?
Huh?
Where is this kid?
I cannot see the kid.
Ah, where are you?
Such good hider.
Wait, I hear someone laughing.
Oh, what's this?
Yeah, I found you.
For sure.
It's my turn now.
You gotta find me.
Yeah, okay, okay.
Kids, huh?
I'm coming.
By the way, how come I don't speak the language here?
This is something we need to answer.
That's a big question.
We woke up...
somewhere from some weird grave...
in the middle of the city.
And we don't speak the language.
How is that?
You know, the kid probably went back to where we started here.
Yeah, I can hear you.
Where are you hiding, huh?
Oh, never mind.
Hey, Cat, have you seen a little kid?
Okay.
Good pets, good talk.
Oh, down here, probably?
Yeah!
Found you!
Yeah, yeah.
Also, I can't help but notice that you actually look a lot like me.
Me must need to go.
Me go now.
Bye.
Oh, he goes to the house.
The house we saw up here.
Let's just call it house.
Me go house?
Yeah.
Me needs to eat, maybe?
I'm gonna assume eat or shower.
I don't know.
Why would a kid need to go home suddenly?
Because it's late.
Curfew.
Right?
Me must need...
Let's just say eat.
All right.
That's very unsure, by the way.
We're gonna put a little thing on that.
All right, see you later, kid.
It was fun.
What?
Oh!
Well, well, well!
Look at that!
Interesting.
Find.
Boom.
This is...
Oh, let me think about this.
Looking.
Searching.
Hiding?
What?
I haven't got any of those.
Oh, that's interesting.
None of this really makes sense to me right now.
Huh?
Found you.
Searching.
Walking.
Hmm.
Well, we now have a special access point.
Let's go to that.
Actually, let's take a small break here.
This game is super cool, man.
I'm blown away by this.
This is fucking fantastic.
I can't wait to play more of this.
I'll just cut it here.
And I'll see you in the next episode.
Bye-bye.